DANYLO SHYSHKOVSKYI



FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Seasoned and independent Front End Developer with 2 years of commercial experience in React application, good knowledge of Design Patterns, Redux, work with API: Rest/Google/Json, implement architecture CSS/ NJK to our project. And always focus on the highest quality of coding

- W My Web Page
- +38 050 849 6986
- +48 796 391 913
- danyloshyshkovskyi@gmail.com
- in /danylo-shyshkovskyi
- Mieszczańska 44, Wroclaw, Poland

EDUCATION

Specialized Secondary School IT Liceum Chernivtsi, Ukraine 2014 - 2018

Introduction to algorithms, learning Pascal, Delphi, and introduction to JAVA, the first acquaintance with creating WEB page using HTML, CSS. Default knowledge of Photoshop.

Bachelor's Degree

WSB we Wroclawiu, Poland 2018 - 2021

Study JavaScript, Java, Python. Creating the first landing page, and the first mobile application, participate in the team creating a web page.

SKILLS

REACT.JS JAVASCRIPT RESTAPI

FIGMA CSS/SASS GIT

REDUX.JS FIREBASE PHOTOSHOP

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER / DESIGNER

2019/11 - 2020/04

Prime tower, Wroclaw, Poland

This job gave me the experience of working in a team ,the ability to use Git, and pretty much advanced my skills in :

- GitHub, GitLab
- Word Press
- Figma

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

2020/05 - 2021/04

Nowatix, Kiev, Ukraine

This company specified on creating landing page for client or one-page websites with dynamic interface and user friendly design. Every day I created minimum 2 small landings with unique design, so my skill are improved in:

- Fast and clear styled pages components end etc by CSS and SASS.
- Working with DOM on JavaScript and jQuery
- CSS architecture SMACSS
- React SPA, HOC technology

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

2021/05 - 2022/02

Abventor, Krakow, Poland

This firm create website by Drupal, where I add my React apps, or use Drupal for backend only, in this company I worked with:

- Drupal
- REST API / JSON API
- React, Redux, Firebase
- Drupal's modules, how implement React app or JS function to website
- Google Api work with google calendar
- TWIG html and NJK architecture

LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate Ukrainian - Native

Polish - Advanced Russian - Native